ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
  - S, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Item 77: Sterling Standard Prints, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against gray background; British symbol for pound in center. 16 x 18.75 cm. Possibly a British firm.
    - Item 78: Sterling Union Lawn, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Lot ________ Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against cream background; British symbol for pound in center. 8.75 x 24.5 cm. (unfolded). Possibly a British firm.
    - Item 79: Stillman & Co. Westerly, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      ____ Yds. Lith. Henry Seibert & Bros. N.Y. Westerly, R.I.: Stillman & Co., ca. 1860s. Black lettering against tan background; image of sheep in center. 6 x 8.75 cm.
    - Item 80: Strafford Manufacturing Co. Cottons, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Forbes & Co. Boston [lithographer]. N.p., ca. 1868-1875. White lettering against blue and red banners; border of gold, red and black. 20.75 x 18.5 cm.
    - Item 81: Suffolk Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Red and gold lettering against white background; red and gold border. 15 x 11.75 cm.
    - Item 82: Suffolk D Blue Drills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Warranted Indigo. George C. Richardson & Co., Boston [dry goods commission merchants]. Yds. N.p., ca. 1865-1885. Black lettering against orange background. 25.25 x 20 cm.
    - Item 83: Suffolk Extra Vest Padding, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Blue lettering and frame against white background. 11.75 x 16 cm.
    - Item 84: Suffolk Manufacturing Company, Lowell, Mass., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      T. R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Lowell, Mass.: Suffolk Manufacturing Company, ca. 1860-1870. Red and gold lettering against white background; image of Native American in center within gold frame; red and gold border. 19.25 x 14 cm.
    - Item 85: Suffolk Silesias, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      London Finish. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against deep purple background. 7.25 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 86: Suiting Stripes, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Image of windmill on edge of water in center, framed by flowers in blue, green and silver. 18 x 23 cm.
    - Item 87: Superfine Finish, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      A l. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering against black background; circular shape. 5 x 5 cm.
    - Item 88: Superior Blue Cottons, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering and frame against orange background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 89: Superior Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Blue lettering and frame; image of house in center with tree in front yard, against white background. 17.75 x 21.25 cm.
    - Item 90: Superior Colored Flannels, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Extra Heavy. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. Yds. N.p., n.d. Red lettering and frame against yellow background. 25.25 x 20.25 cm.
    - Item 91: Superior Cottons For Family Use, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering and border against green background. 12.5 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 92: The Superior 1010 Satin Drill, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Probably British, ca. 1900s. Silhouette image of two children exclaiming over birthday cake with ten candles in center; white lettering against green background and black banners. 18 x 22.75 cm.
    - Item 93: Herald. Superior Quality Both Sides Finished Alike, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      No. ____ N.p., n.d. Image of herald blowing trumpet in center. Orange background, circular shape. 6.5 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 94: Superior Robe Linen, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; frame of red and gold surrounding center Image of young woman wearing veil anchored on the back of her head with flowers. Identical in style to Item 95, in this folder, except image of young woman is different. 13 x 17.5 cm.
    - Item 95: Superior Robe Linen, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; frame of red and gold surrounding center Image of young woman wearing choker around her neck and a maroon hat with flowers on her head. Identical in style to Item 94, in this folder, except image of young woman is different. 13 x
    - Item 96: Superior Wigans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering and elaborate frame against light tan background. 18 x 14 cm.
    - Item 97: Sutton's Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Quality No. ___ Pat. ____ Size ____. [North Andover, Mass.]: Sutton's Mills, ca. 1800s. Black lettering against white background; heraldic crest in center with Tout Jours Prest written on banner. 11.25 x 8.25 cm.
    - Item 98: Sutton's superior heavy twilled cassimeres, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Case, Yds. Philadelphia (Manayunk), Pa.: Charles Sutton, Perseverance Mills, before 1870. Red lettering against white background; image of Perseverance Mills in center. 7.5 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 99: Swift River Tickings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      ____ Yds. Millbury, Mass.: Cordis Mills, ca. 1870s. Image of four drummer boys dressed in Civil War uniforms (Union blue) 20 x 25 cm.
    - Item 100: Swift River Tickings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      ____ Yds. Millbury, Mass.: Cordis Mills, ca. 1870s. Image of four drummer boys dressed in Civil War uniforms (Union blue) 20 x 25 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 101: Swiss Dots, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 6)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Image of young woman wearing hat and carrying basket of flowers feeding goat; Swiss-stype chalet in background. 7.5 x 10 cm.
  - T, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: T.H & S., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; crest and shield in center with leopard (?) on top in gold against white background. 8.5 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 2: Taken By All, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      N.p., n.d. United States of America Trade Dollar, 420 Grains 900 Fine in center with image of eagle. Silver lettering against black background. 9.25 x 11.75 cm.
    - Item 3: Talbot Mills royal blue R ____Yds., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Talbot Mills. Royal Blue R. ____ Yds. [North Billerica, Mass.]: Talbot Mills, n.d. Black lettering against cream background. 3 x 5.25 cm.
    - Item 4: Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talloura, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Style ____ Shade ____ Case No. ____ Piece No. ____ Yds. ____. Printed on reverse is: No allowance will be made on this piece of goods after it is cut. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, ca. 1900-1957. Black lettering with image of sheep's head agains
    - Item 5: Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talloura, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 6: Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talloura, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 7: Talbot Mills Established 1857: Talloura, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 8: Talbot Mills. Royal Blue, L, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      ___ Yds. North Billerica, Mass.: Talbot Mills, n.d. Black lettering against cream background; the letter "L" is printed within a diamond. 3 x 5.25 cm.
    - Item 9: These Goods Are Manufactured From Yarns Of Extra Twist, And Are Recommended For Strength And Durability, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against light gray background within gold frame. 19 x 10 cm.
    - Item 10: These Goods Are Manufactured From Yarns Of Extra Twist, And Are Recommended For Strength And Durability, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against light gray background within gold frame. Copy 2. 19 x 10 cm.
    - Item 11: This Material Has Been Shrunk, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering against white background. 11.5 x 6.25 cm.
    - Item 12: Thistle Balmoral, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Forbes & Co. Entered according to Act of Congress in the year 1873 by Forbes Co. in the office of the Librarian at Washington. N.p., 1873. White and Red lettering against black background, with thistle plant in center. 10.75 x 14.25 cm.
    - Item 13: Thistle Mills., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Ilchester, Md.: Thistle Mills, ca. 1900s. Red and white lettering against black background, with thistle plant in center. 16 x 19.5 cm.
    - Item 14: Thistle Mills. Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      No. Yds. Ilchester, Md.: Thistle Mills, ca. 1900s. Gold, green and blue lettering against white background. 11.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 15: Thistle Mills A Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Ilchester, Md.: Thistle Mills, ca. 1900s. Gold, red and black lettering against white background, within elaborate gold, red and black frame. 10 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 16: Thorndike Company, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Palmer, Mass.: Thorndike Company, ca. 1800s. Red, gold and black lettering against white background, within red, gold and black frame. The letters T Co are intertwined at the center bottom. 16 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 17: Thorndike Company, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      T. R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Palmer, Mass.: Thorndike Company, ca. 1860- 1900. Gold lettering against white background, within gold and gray-striped frame. old damage at top of label. 14.5 x 18 cm.
    - Item 18: Thorn River Mills Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Warranted 64x64. No. ____ Yds. ____. Forbes Co. Boston. N.p., ca. 1868- 1875. White lettering and image of glove against red background. 10.25 x 15 cm.
    - Item 19: Tick Tock Ticks, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Trautmann, Bailey & Blampey, N.Y. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white banners, in red and gold frame. 21 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 20: Tiger Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Image of tiger in center; white lettering against brown border. 23 x 17 cm.
    - Item 21: Tiger Blue Drills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering and border against orange background. 23.5 x 19.75 cm.
    - Item 22: Tip Top Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Red lettering against green background. 20 x 16.25 cm.
    - Item 23: Tip Top Superfine Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against white background. 12 x 17.5 cm.
    - Item 24: Tiverton Print Works. Warranted Fast Colours, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      No. _____ ____ Yds. Tiverton, R.I.: Tiverton Print Works, ca. 1835-1839. Image of woman at center with towel (?) over her right arm and a sheaf or quill in her left hand, leaning on a shield on which is printed Warranted Fast Colours. 7.25 x 6.25 cm.
    - Item 25: Toile du Nord [Northern Star], Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Trade Mark. Parkhill Munfacturing Company. No. Yds. Fitchburg, Mass.: Parkhill Mfg. Co., ca. 1900. Black lettering with gold star in center and gold border. 8 x 11.25 cm.
    - Item 26: Tremont corset jeans., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      T. R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Lowell, Mass.: Tremont and Suffolk Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering against white background within red and gold border. Mold damage at bottom of label. 16 x 13.25 cm. Identical to Items 27-29, in this folder, except for
    - Item 27: Tremont corset jeans., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      T. R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Lowell, Mass.: Tremont and Suffolk Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering against white background within red and gold border. Mold damage at bottom of label. 16 x 13.25 cm. Identical to Items 26 and 28-29, in this folder, exce
    - Item 28: Tremont Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      T. R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Lowell, Mass.: Tremont and Suffolk Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering against white background within red and gold border. Mold damage at bottom of label. 16 x 13.25 cm. Identical to Items 26-27 and 29, in this folder, exce
    - Item 29: Tremont Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      T. R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Lowell, Mass.: Tremont and Suffolk Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering against white background within red and gold border. Mold damage at bottom of label. 16 x 13.25 cm. Identical to Items 26-28, in this folder, except for
    - Item 30: Tremont Mills Blue Drills. Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works,Somerville, Mass. Lowell, Mass.: Tremont Mills, ca. 1831-1871. Black lettering with image of horse in center against orange background. 24 x 19.5 cm.
    - Item 31: Tremont Mills Blue Sheetings. Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. Lowell, Mass.: Tremont Mills, ca. 1831-1871. Black lettering against yellow background. 25 x 20.25 cm.
    - Item 32: Tremont Mills superior canton flannels, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Yards. B.H. Penhallow, Printer, Lowell. Lowell, Mass.: Tremont Mills, ca. 1860. Brown lettering against white background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 33: Twilled Linings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 7)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and frame against white background. 15.25 x 14 cm.
  - U, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Uncasville Manufacturing Company., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Montville, Conn.: Uncasville Manufacturing Company, ca. 1850-1900. Gold lettering with image of native American in center against light tan background. 21.5 x 13.75 cm.
    - Item 2: Under the Rose, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Image of rose at center with two seated angels beneath. Gold lettering against cream background. Identical to Item 3, in this folder, except for color. 12 x 14.75 cm.
    - Item 3: Under the Rose, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Image of rose at center with two seated angels beneath. Gold lettering against cream background. Identical to Item 2, in this folder, except for color. 12 x 14.75 cm.
    - Item 4: Union Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. T.R. Marvin & Son, Prs. N.p., ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering against deep blue background. 12 x 17.5 cm.
    - Item 5: Union Mills Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. T.R. Marvin & Son, Prs. N.p., ca. 1860-1900. Gold lettering and frame against white background. 12 x 17.5 cm.
    - Item 6: Union Lawn, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Lot ______Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and gold oval in center against white/cream background. 8.5 x 24.75 cm. (unfolded).
    - Item 7: Union Lawns, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      F.C. Paxson & Co. Phila. [printer?]. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against gold background with image of eagle in center. 12 x 17 cm.
    - Item 8: Union Mills Linings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering against white background within green and gold frame. Identical to Item 9, in this folder, except for colors of frame. 7.75 x 10.25 cm.
    - Item 9: Union Mills Linings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering against white background within green and gold frame. Identical to Item 8, in this folder, except for colors of frame. 7.75 x 10.25 cm.
    - Item 10: Union Mills Superior Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Expressly For Tailors' Use. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering against white background, within gold and red frame. Identical to Item 11, in this folder, except for frame colors. 7.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 11: Union Mills Superior Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Expressly For Tailors' Use. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering against white background, within gold and red frame. Identical to Item 10, in this folder, except for frame colors. 7.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 12: Twilled Silesia, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Union Manufacturing Co. N.p., n.d. Embossed; black lettering in cream oval surrounded by gold frame. 9.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 13: Union Prints Warranted Madder Colors, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      North Adams Mass. North Adams, Mass., n.d. Gold lettering and design against white background. 9.5 x 12.25 cm.
    - Item 14: Union Mills, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Manufactured by A. Campbell & Co. No. ____ ____ Yds. C. Reen, Lith, Phila. Philadelphia (Manayunk), Pa.: A. Campbell & Co., ca. 1870. Image of mill complex on river Written on reverse of label: "Ezra this is Another view of the Mill where I work. You
    - Item 15: Utica family sheetings, sheets and pillow cases extra heavy., Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Utica, N.Y.: Utica Steam Cotton Mills, ca. 1850-1900. Gold lettering and image of mill buildings against white background. 20 x 14.5 cm.
  - V, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Velvets: Brilliant Silk Finish, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Manufactured of Superior Material in such a manner that a most perfect lustre is obtained which approaches more nearly to the Lyons silk velvets. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering and design against white background. 14.5 x 22.5 cm.
    - Item 2: Verona Cambric Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and design against black background. Identical to Item 3, in this folder, except for background color. 10 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 3: Verona Cambric Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and design against black background. Identical to Item 2, in this folder, except for background color. 10 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 4: Verus Ad Finem, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Embossesd; figure of arm holding branch in center in gold, gold border against green background. Letters underneath center image are unknown, C & Co. 9.75 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 5: Best Grade Vest Paddings, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Yards. N.p., n.d. Black lettering and border against white background. 10 x 15.25 cm.
    - Item 6: Victoria Fine Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Glove Finish. W. H. Forbes & Co. [lithographer]. N.p., ca. 1868-1875. Black lettering and border against white background. 14 x 10 cm.
    - Item 7: Virtue will be rewarded, Cloth label (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Registered trade mark. No. 101933. N.d. Gold wording and arm holding hammer in center; red background. May have been used by J. & P. Coats; this is a British label. 9.5 x 10.5 cm.
  - W, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: W.W. Crichton & Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Manchester. N.p., n.d. Probably Manchester, England. Embossed; image of young boy in tartan in center with rifle on his shoulder and his dog. 9.75 x 13 cm.
    - Item 2: W.W. Crichton & Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Manchester. N.p., n.d. Probably Manchester, England. Embossed; image of young woman and man in ballet (?) costume in center. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 3: W.W. Crichton & Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Manchester. N.p., n.d. Probably Manchester, England. Embossed; image of young woman riding sidesaddle on donkey. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 4: W.W. Crichton & Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Manchester. N.p., n.d. Probably Manchester, England. Embossed; image of woman carrying basket of food on her head getting a shoeshine from shoeshine boy. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 5: W.W. Crichton & Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Manchester. N.p., n.d. Probably Manchester, England. Embossed; image of girl standing by seesaw with two boys on it. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 6: W.W. Crichton & Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Manchester. N.p., n.d. Probably Manchester, England. Embossed; image of man getting simultaneous shoeshines from two shoeshine boys. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 7: W.W. Crichton & Co., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Manchester. N.p., n.d. Probably Manchester, England. Embossed; image of two girls in center, one in blue dress wearing hat, the other in a red dress, with a crown of flowers in her hair. 10 x 13 cm.
    - Item 8: Wacantuck long cloth., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Uxbridge, Mass.: Waucantuck Mills, ca. 1860-1900. Image of mill complex in center, surrounded by copper lettering and border. 15.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 9: Wachusett cassimere, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. Yds. Worcester, Mass.: Wachusett Mills, ca. 1888-1908. Gold lettering against blue background; large eagle in center perched on packing crate, with mill complex, railroad and sailing ship in background. 9.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 10: Walden Denim, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against red banners; image (engraved?) of mill complex in center; gold, brown and red border. 24.5 x 19.75 cm.
    - Item 11: Waltham Bleachery and Dye Works., Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Waltham, Mass.: Waltham Bleachery and Dye Works, ca. 1900s. Red and gold lettering within red and gold border against white background. 7.5 x 5.25 cm.
    - Item 12: Waltham Extra Wide Sheeting, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black, gold and red lettering within elaborate red and gold border against white background; image of Native American in shield at center. 19 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 13: Wamsutta Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      New Bedford, Mass.: Wamsutta Mills, ca. 1850-1900. Engraved? Image of mill complex on harbor with railroad on shore. Gray lettering against white background. 22 x 15 cm.
    - Item 14: Seaside shirting Wamsutta Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      The Forbes Lith. M'f'g. Co. Boston. New Bedford, Mass.: Wamsutta Mills, ca. 1875-1900. Images of four girls playing near beached ship called the "Busy Bee"; black and white engraving. 23.75 x 19.75 cm.
    - Item 15: Wamsutta Mills, 1867; Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Notice: Buyers of Goods under the names of Wamsutta Prints, Checks, Lindseys, Cambrics, Ticks and Silesias, are hereby informed that all such goods are not manufactured at the Wamsutta Mills. We limit our Name and the Wamsutta Ticket to our Shirtings and
    - Item 16: Wamsutta Prints, Madder Colors, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Engraving? Image of mill complex in center; black lettering; Native Americans in bottom two corners. 13.75 x 17 cm.
    - Item 17: Warranted 64 x 64 Extra, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and border against cream background. 12 x 5.5 cm.
    - Item 18: Warranted Best Extra 64 x 64 Cloths Superior Color & Finish, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black script lettering against cream background. 12 x 7 cm.
    - Item 19: Warranted Fast Color, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; image of harpist in white against gold background in center; gold lettering and border against white background. 9 x 12 cm.
    - Item 20: Warranted Pure Finish, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against red background; gold border. 11 x 5.5 cm.
    - Item 21: Warranted Pure Indigo, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. White lettering against red and gold background. 18.5 x 5.5 cm.
    - Item 22: Warranted Showerproof, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Blue script lettering on banner; very thin paper. 18 x 7.5 cm. Identical to Item 23, in this folder, except for color of lettering.
    - Item 23: Warranted Showerproof, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Blue script lettering on banner; very thin paper. 18 x 7.5 cm. Identical to Item 22, in this folder, except for color of lettering.
    - Item 24: Warranted All Superior Finish, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering and crest within gold frame against white background. 9 x 12.25 cm.
    - Item 25: Warren Cotton Mills, Cloth label (Box 4, Folder 1)